<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Emele Delivery App</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">Login</string>
    <string name="_22_duong_so_147_phuoc_long_b_quan_9_thanh_pho_ho_chi_minh">22, Duong so 147, Phuoc Long B, Quan 9, Thanh Pho Ho Chi Minh</string>
    <string name="sort_by"> Sort by:</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="facebook_app_id">283740247620840</string>
    <string name="default_web_client_id">23209393665-9ml2662fsia935p4b0a2nkdu3ru4p9j3.apps.googleusercontent.com</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="cancelordermsg">We will continue to improve our service and satisfy you on the next order.</string>
    <string name="cancelorderPopup">We are so sad about your cancellation</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_text">USER TERMS OF USE\n\nI. Definitions and Interpretation\nELEME application ("ELEME") is a mobile application providing e-commerce platform food delivery service, operated by ELEME DEVELOPER STUDENT GROUP ("Group"). The application helps to connect food providers, delivery service providers, and those who need to use food delivery service ("Service")\n\nCustomers: are individuals and organizations requesting to use food delivery service using ELEME to post a notice of demand for food delivery to purchase\n\nRiders: are food delivery service providers using ELEME to connect with customers and the restaurants\n\nRestaurants: are individuals and organizations listed on ELEME, with or without the demand of advertising and selling food, who may provide the food that Customers request\n\nUsers: are individuals and organizations registering to use ELEME Application\n\nFood delivery service: is a food delivery service traded through ELEME\n\nIntellectual property: is any patent, copyright, registered or unregistered design, rights to the design, registered or unregistered trademarks, service marks or public ownership, industrial or other intellectual property, including applications for any of the above.\n\nII. General Regulations\nApplication name of E-commerce trading floor service provider: ELEME\nThe Users are individuals, organizations, having demand for ordering food/drink online. The users must register in accordance with legal regulations and be recognized by Management of ELEME DEVELOPER STUDENT GROUP .\nFood dealt on ELEME meets full conditions on food safety and regulations.\nRestaurants are completely responsible for all services and products supplied by themselves to Customers, which are already ordered through use of the services provided by ELEME.\nWhen Users and/or Restaurants access ELEME to demand, request, or/and provide Service, User and/or Restaurant already agree to comply with and be bound by the regulations on ELEME operation.\nUpon taking part in ELEME, Users and Restaurants must learn about their legal responsibilities under Vietnam’s current laws by themselves and commit to their responsibilities in the Regulation of ELEME.\n\nIII. Installation, Registration &amp; Transaction\nInstallation Process:\nStep 1: Download and install ELEME Application depending on the device you are using\nStep 2: Once downloaded successfully click ELEME Application to start\nStep 3: For the first time of opening ELEME Application, the Application will request to click allow for sending notification and having access to the user’s location. Press "Allow" to continue.\n\nRegistration Process:\nStep 1: Click at the top-right corner of the Application to move to Login page\nStep 2: Choose either "Connect with Mobile Number" or "Connect with Facebook" depending on the preference\nStep 2a-1: (for Connect with Mobile Number): Enter currently using a mobile phone number, and then press "next" to receive a verification number\nStep 2a-2: Enter Name, E-mail address, desired password\nStep 2b-1: (for Connect with Facebook): Press "Continue" when the Application asks "ELEME" wants to use "facebook.com" to sign in\nStep 2b-2: Press "Continue as [name]"\nStep 2b-3: Enter currently using a mobile phone number, and then press "next" to receive a verification number\nStep 2b-4: Enter the received verification number\nStep 2b-5: Enter Name, E-mail address, desired password.</string>
</resources>